Okay, it's time to see what Codex did in 15 minutes when I quipped with the same prompt as the others.
But first, let's do a quick recap. Shall we not? Let me begin by showing you again the
GSD. Not the first one we did. It was the second one we did, I think, but GSD, which was the most
thorough five hours, five hours in the making. This was what we got, this is quite professional looking one, a bit less
flashy than some of the others, let's just do a quick buy three apple, let's see what
happens, there it appears. Now that I understand this funny thing that confuse you about this
chart, I guess we should try clicking here. Now that doesn't make any difference, I was
wondering if that was going to make it appear on the chart here. Oh look, it changes the
title up there, so maybe it is working, we just have to leave it a bit perhaps. Maybe that's how that's meant to work.
And let's just try here by three shares of Goog and make sure that that works.
And it's thinking, hopefully that's going to work. Yeah, executed. It's got a very nice looking thing there,
and there's some Google. Okay, that was number one. And now I want to show you the Claude Agents one.
Check this one out.
It looks really nice.
I like the way that all of this flashes like this.
And if I click there, yeah, okay, so I guess I just didn't get this, the first time I saw
these are interface because you click here and this updates and I think you have to
wait a while for this chart to start appearing.
But I totally didn't realize that. And we can say here, please purchase one share of JPM.
See what happens there.
There we go, it's bought one, J.P. Morgan.
There we have it, very nice.
Okay, so this one here is the Claude Agents one,
my favorite one to work with.
I like the user interface as well.
I'm not sure what you think.
Looks very nice.
Now we'll switch to the next one, which is the gas town one.
We just saw this.
They all look quite similar.
This is the interaction that we already just had.
Just to flip through them again.
I'm getting confused, but this is GSD, Claude Agents, and then this one is gas town.
Those are the three. It's hard to keep it together
They look very similar and of course not a big surprise. It was opus 4.6 building them all just
orchestrated differently and with the first one taking five hours that maybe it overworked it
Okay, and now I'm going to show you codex
Different orchestration and a different look here. We have it. Wow, it does look different.
I mean, it has a lot of similarities.
It has the same kind of,
the same kind of black look
and the same flashing thing over here.
But I gotta tell you,
I think this is really nice.
It might be because sometimes a change
just looks better, you know?
But I think this looks great.
I love the effect of these here.
They look really professional,
really sleek.
This user interface just looks very, very nice.
And so I love it.
It's very similar, but this chart is clearly improved.
And yeah, now when I flick through,
I see it changing, very nice indeed.
Really impressive, I love it.
And let's ask it to do a trade.
Let's buy one share of meta.
Let's see what happens. Order place, if I want a share of meta. Let's see what happens. Order place by one share of meta and there's meta and it's happening.
So it's very nice. I like the way the portfolio updates so far.
So they all do that. Yes, they are. Of course they are.
Oh, but not this one. Check that out.
That looks like a small bug that we have there with my phone wrong.
Lord agents, maybe not so good after all.
And is this one updating? No, nor is GSD. with my phone or on Lord agents. Maybe not so good after all.
And is this one updating?
No, nor is GSD.
So the only ones that were able to keep the portfolio,
oh no look there, the portfolio's gone static.
So it looks like this is something
that opening eyes codecs one on that front.
It has something really nice there.
So some great implementations,
to my surprise, I've got to tell you
that actually the codecs implementation,
codecs 5.3 this is, is perhaps my personal winner, a late breaking surprise. And this is the,
the only one that didn't, that didn't use the, we didn't have the skills, so we didn't give it the
extra skill to know how to use it. So rebrass, although it seems to have figured everything out.
And it's, yeah, the one that just took 15 minutes.
It was the fastest to build and it came up with perhaps,
perhaps, I've been in the best outcome,
but you should tell me what you think.
Your best outcome is, please put your notes
in the chat, let me know what you think,
and hopefully you're experimenting with this yourself.
And here I have to show you one more time,
the final results.
This is the codecs version.
But you'll see something's different here.
You'll see first of all, everything that's quite green.
And secondly, you'll see that there's not much going on.
It doesn't appear to be flashing just every so often.
And there's a few reasons for that.
One of them is that I have just switched
to using the true polygon now massive market data
so that this is actually showing real live market data.
This is the real stock price of JP Morgan right now.
The reasons all a bit green is that this is
after hours at the moment.
It is just past trading cut off.
So there's not much happening.
There's some after hours activity,
which is why there are occasional changes.
If we were during the middle of the trading day,
you would see more action.
But it's pretty cool that you are looking
at real stock prices here.
This is now the actual platform
that is showing a true market data simulator
with the real results coming through.
And it wasn't just a matter of changing
the putting in the polygon, the massive key,
because it didn't work first time,
because the code that Claude wrote didn't actually
work immediately. It had a wrong hard coded key in there. And I told Codex, Codex found
the problem, fixed it. And then Codex told me, hey, you realize it's after trading hours,
it's going to be a bit static. There'll be a bit of after hours movement. And of course,
Codex was exactly right. And so in conclusion, what you're looking at really is a kind of modern day simulated trading environment,
a modern Bloomberg-esque terminal with a position heat map with an AI chat with real
live market data that's just flashing occasionally as after hours trading activity occurs.
And it's pretty impressive all in all.
All of these solutions are pretty impressive. But for me, as it happens, whilst
as you could probably tell, Cloud Code is my favorite platform. I love the tooling. I will
say that on this occasion, at least I believe that codex emerges as the leader of the pack.
But wait, there's more. There's always one more thing. And here is the one more thing.
Let's let's I'm back in a terminal again. Let's go sprite list to see
our list of sprites that we've got running. We've just got the one called finally worker.
And I do sprite minus s finally worker console to a reattach to that sprite running in the
cloud. There we are. We are now running. We are using SSH. We we are we are remoted in to the sprite running in the cloud. And I've
mentioned a few times something called T-MARKS, which is something that you can run on Linux and
Mac systems that lets you take a terminal and break it into multiple terminals. I'll put the
commands and the resources. I've set up a T-MARKS so that there are four consoles running and I can
reattach to them at any point. And I've called it quad because it divides things into quads and now I can type T-mocks, attach minus T quad to reattach to my four terminals that have
been running. And here they are, bam, four terminals for you. So what do I have
here? I have four different terminals. I can flip between them in T-mocks by
doing ctrl B and then right to go to the right-hand one, ctrl B and down
arrow keys to go to the bottom right, Control B and left to go over there,
Control B up and I'm back up at the top left again.
It's very similar to the Control B up and down
that we did when we were moving between T-MARK's sessions
before and I've got four different terminal windows.
The one on the top left is running codex,
codex in YOLO mode.
The one on the top right is running Claude
in dangerously skip permissions mode, which is it's yellow
mode.
Bottom left is another codecs.
I've got two codecs is running and the bottom right I'm using for my Git workflow to check
things in.
But even so this is like three different coding agents running.
But within that the codecs on the top left is running codecs with subagents activated. So it can use agents to run multiple things.
And as well you know,
Cloud is able to use Cloud Agent Teams
so that Cloud can run a bunch of agents,
or of course it can also use subagents.
So we've got this kind of ability
to have three different kind of heads
that we're talking to that can have themselves
gangs of agents.
And I have just been riffing with this
for the last couple of hours.
And I've mostly been doing market data work and back-end work with codecs on the top
left and UI stuff with Claude on the top right and I've been tracking stuff and mark
down files using that best practice.
I've been keeping things together and they've been making great progress together as a team
and it's been quite hard work managing everything going on.
But I've always been the boss.
I've just been telling them what to do.
I've not dug into the code.
I've just asked them to look at things
and occasionally review each other's stuff too.
So powerful.
And we've made tons of progress.
And it's one more time for me to mention to you
this thing, this frame of mind you have to be in
that you can often make tons of progress
in a short amount of time. You feel like you
are on fire. You've had your 10x in your performance. You really are. And then you hit
like a like a block, a roadblock or some sort of bug. And and the agents just keep hitting
the same problem and can't get their way through it. And you find that you spend a
lot of time just getting over a small obstacle. And you can feel like, ah, I'm wasting all of my time. It's not this 10x,
but you have to keep in mind still even when you factor that in. The amount of time that it's
taken me to make lots of progress, a couple of hours, is still multiple times two or three times
faster than if I was writing all this myself. So never be surprised when that initial 10X then gets pulled back by some bugs keep in mind it's
still a significant net positive.
So that is my important message to you to keep fuel in the tank to be ready to hit
problems and expect to spend a lot of your time, a large bush of your time, carefully
reproducing, get down the issue, let's understand the issue before we fix it, make a markdown file,
explaining the issue, and now fix it,
and now test and prove you fixed it.
That process, and even then discovering
the problem's still there,
and I said, "No, you didn't fix it."
That can take time, be ready for that,
expect it, it is part of the new way.
Okay, that's enough preamble,
it's time for me to reveal to you
the fruits of the labor, not of me,
but of these coding agents.
This is the result of a few coding agents, each with multiple sub agents.
A few hours of work.
Let's see it.
Here I present to you the finally or thin ally trader workstation with live market data
courtesy of massive.
You are looking at a watch list of 60 stock tickers divided into tech, financials,
health care, consumer, industrials and energy. They are being live updated as the markets change.
You are looking at the live ticker of Apple on the display there. You are looking at the portfolio
P&L and our heat map and the LLM chat. This, this is our trader workstation. Let's agree. This is sensational.
And it will come as no surprise to you to see
that now I can click on one of these tickers
and zoom in on it and see on the right
the main chart of what's going on.
There is Netflix.
Is it to be having a bit of a journey downwards there?
So you see everything that is happening
on this dashboard.
Absolutely amazing.
And there's one more little trick to show you.
Claude added this little feature which I will show you now which is this symbol up here
in case you are somewhat tired of these like gamer style dark mode UIs, you can flip it
to light mode.
Check that out, it just looks so fresh and professional and clean.
It's like wow and flip it back to dark mode again if that's your preferred style.
Light mode and dark mode.
Done just like that.
I am floored by this.
It is just fantastic.
I kid you not if you'd shown me this a couple of years ago and asked me how long it would take to build this.
I don't know what you'd have said.
I probably said this would take me a month or two.
I would have charged a fair amount of money for this.
Even though it's, I'd still argue it's probably still a demo app in the,
there aren't, there isn't a user login side of it yet and you can't deploy it yet.
Those are pretty easy steps now because it's all in a Docker container.
Those are just small steps to take this into a proper commercial app.
So I would probably say this is a month or two worth of work for me and it would have been a really
hard project and it was just super easy.
It honestly was.
And hopefully you've got the same kinds of results.
Hopefully you're building that look towards building something like this.
I'll put in the course resources how you could get, of course, exactly this code base
and see it for yourself.
But it's much more fun to build it yourself or do something different.
Do something that takes it in a different direction
that you like but with a similar wow factor that this has and then by all means add to your
agent that it should deploy it, deploying a container is relatively easy, they'll walk you
through the instructions and help you make any decisions you need to make about which
vendor you use and then you can have this live on the internet to just a brilliant project and just a great capstone finale moment for us.